A woman and her two young children were seen outside The SCOAN,
distressed and in a very emotional state late at night.
The attention of the Emmanuel TV team was called to their case and they came to find out what had happened
to this family.
Let us listen to them.
My name is Christie Pua.
I came from Indonesia.
And who are the two people standing beside you?
They are my children; Fredrick and Blessing.
Can you explain the reason why you have come to The SCOAN this evening?
I am looking for favour from the man of God.
We have been living here.
We have run from the village because they accused my husband for being a murderer -
that he killed his own father.
After a few months, his niece died and they accused my husband for being the murderer who killed his niece.
That is why we ran away from the village to Lagos without anything.
We managed to sell the remaining things in the house only for the transport money.
Now, we have become like beggars in Lagos – we don't have any place to stay.
That is why we ran here – we want to look for the favour of the man of God.
Who is the father of the children?
His name is John Ken Egesi from Imo State.
I have been married to him for the past 16 years.
How did you meet with him?
We met in Indonesia when he was doing his business.
He was selling garments and exporting clothes.
Some years after we married, he said I should come and be introduced to his family in Nigeria.
I have been here for the past five years, living in Imo State with him, suffering.
The worst part now is that they accused my husband of murdering his own father and niece.
That is why we are here now.
We have no other place.
My husband is just hustling.
Sometimes he goes to Alaba and at the end of the day, he brings only 100 or 200 naira.
How can we eat with 200 naira with these kids?
Every day, we have to pay for the lodging place.
Now, they have asked us to pack out and we have no other place to stay.
How old are your children?
This one is thirteen years old and this one is five years old.
Please, man of God, help us!
Help my little family!
Where is your husband now?
I don't know where he is.
He went out in the morning as usual, hustling and he knows that we no longer have any place to stay.
I just decided that I cannot live like this any longer.
My name is Frederick.
I was born in Indonesia, then, we came to Nigeria.
Frederick Egesi.
Since that time, me and my mother and sister have always suffered, all the time.
Sometimes, we cannot eat and we didn't know what to do any longer.
In the village, they accused my father of killing somebody.
That was the problem that brought us to Lagos.
Food is very hard for us to get.
Before we eat…
In our hotel, we don't have money so, we are owing them.
They have sent us out.
They are telling us to pack out because we have not paid their money.
The money we owe them is a lot.
Since two months, we have been in Lagos and to eat is very hard.
My daddy – I don’t know where he is.
He went out in the morning and has not come back.
He used to go to Alaba and help people so they will give him money.
That is the only thing he used to do.
Sometimes, he will come back empty handed.
He would not hold any money.
Then, we will not eat.
We will just sleep until the next day.
He will be always owing people.
Now, we have a lot of debts to pay.
We owe a lot of people now.
This is our bag because they seized our other bag.
They seized it because we have not paid the hotel accommodation fee.
They seized it so this is the only bag we use to manage and come out.
DEEPLY EMOTIONAL Video That Will Make You CRY!
My sister's clothes, my mother's and my own clothes and a blanket.
These are the only things you have for you and your family?
Yes, the only things we have.
I came with my own passport but my two kids don't have any ID with them right now.
It is only me who has my own passport.
Can we see your documents?
Yes, of course.
DEEPLY EMOTIONAL Video That Will Make You CRY!
This is my passport.
It is only I who has a passport.
When we came to Nigeria, we used Travel Certificates.
Since then, they don’t have any ID, only I do.
We don’t have any money because since we came to Nigeria, nothing is working for us - nothing at all.
Please, we are coming here because we know there is solution in this very place – The SCOAN.
We used to see on Emmanuel TV that the man of God used to help people.
That is why this is our last bus stop.
I believe man of God, that our case will not run from you.
I believe you will help us.
I don’t even have one naira with me now, as I am talking.
Even my kids have not eaten since afternoon – we only had a little breakfast this morning.
Please, man of God, help us!
My name is Blessing.
My daddy is not around – he went to Alaba.
He is looking for money.
No food – we don’t have money.
The first thing the Emmanuel TV team did on hearing their pitiful plight was to take them in, give them a good
hot meal, something to drink, and the place to stay for the night.
Our first response as Christians is love.
No matter what situation we find ourselves in or what situation we are presented with; we should love first,
and walk in the light of love.
Love is the greatest because God is love.
After meeting Mrs Egesi and her children, SCOAN representatives called Mr Egesi,
to inform him of their whereabouts.
He responded by also making his way to the church.
The following Sunday, they came out to share their heart-rendering experience.
Let's listen to them.
My name is Christie Pua.
I'm from Indonesia.
I'm 37 years old.
These are my children, Frederick and Blessing; he is 13 years old and she is 5 years old.
The man standing beside them is John Kennedy Egesi, my husband.
I met my husband in Indonesia about 16 years ago, when he was doing business in my country.
Since then, we have been married.
My son Frederick was born in Jakarta (Indonesia) and this one was born in Pakistan.
After some years of our marriage, my husband decided to bring us to Nigeria to meet his parents.
I didn't know that on our coming to Nigeria everything would just turn around.
Nothing worked for us to the extent that we began to suffer greatly.
I never imagined that we would suffer so much in Nigeria; it was too much for me.
Even every day I had to cook with firewood, so I had to fetch wood from around the compound.
If that was not enough, the remaining wood I would give to my son to sell, to get money.
She said, ever since then she had never expected this kind of difficulties that she, her children and husband
have been going through.
Because of these terrible difficulties they have been going through, every morning she had to go to the bush
to fetch firewood, and after fetching the firewood she was giving some of it to her son to go around the street
to try to sell it, in order to make money for them to meet their daily needs.
Not only firewood, when it was the season for aboli, I would pick it around the compound.
I would clean it, then send my son to take it to sell at the market or if there was eko,
I would clean it and send him to sell it in the marker.
All the things I did were to help feed me and my children.
It's not only me who suffered but my son, he would go to dustbins to pick bottles and things for him to sell
to help me – to earn a small amount of money from it.
They dropped out of school for a long time.
For us to even eat was very difficult, talk less of taking them to school.
As if all the suffering I went through, for me past five years in Nigeria, was not enough;
our condition continued to get worse as time went on.
When my father-in-law died, they accused my husband that he killed my father-in-law.
After a few months, the niece died and they also accused my husband that he killed the niece as well.
Before, it was sad but now things have become more tough again, tougher than before.
After everything that has happened, I cannot bear it again.
I would plead with my husband every day,
“Please, I don’t want to lose our lives in this village, I want to live.
I have left my county for so many years, I still have my family there.
I don’t want to return only by name.
It’s better we secure our lives, anything we gather we can sell it.”
We sold our television and generator for us to get transport to come to Lagos to secure our lives.
That is why we are here in Lagos.
We suffered and ran from the village, when we reached Lagos, we still suffered.
That is what made us to come to The SCOAN to look for help from the man of God.
Please, man of God.
Man of God help me and my family.
I want to go back to my country; I don’t want to live in Nigeria any more.
Five years is enough for me, please man of God.
How can I continue living like this?
I don’t want to and I cannot.
Even the clothes that I and my children are wearing, someone gave them to us.
Think about that kind of life – I don’t want it, please man of God.
There was a clip to show how she was suffering; she was going to the bush, gathering some firewood
in order to cook for her family.
Yet, the suffering still continued.
Since we arrived in Lagos my husband tried to hustle and would go out every morning,
hustling to get money for us to eat.
But after much effort my husband would return with only 100 or 200 at the highest 500 naira.
What can we use that money for when we need to eat and pay for accommodation?
My name is Frederick, this is my mother, sister and my father.
Since the day we came to Nigeria we have been suffering – all the time.
To the extent that I would go to the bush to pick things to sell.
Bottles and other things just to help my mother.
I’m not going to school, even my sister is not going to school; we have dropped out for a long time.
I want the man of God to help us so we can leave this country, we have suffered a lot.
Please man of God, help us.
My name is John Kennedy Egasi
I am from Imo State, Nigeria.
The people beside me are my wife, son and little daughter.
We lived abroad for a long time but after some time, I decided to bring my family home.
I brought them home, everything was fine before I came home.
But all of a sudden, when I came home everything turned around.
Things started going bad; nothing was working out.
Even to the extent that they accused me of killing my father who we had been taking care of.
How can I kill my father?
They accused me and started calling me names and all sorts.
When the insults became too much – we couldn’t take it anymore, we decided to come to Lagos.
We sold our generator, television and things to get to Lagos.
When we got to Lagos, we tried to find a place to stay that would cost little like 1,500 naira.
We stayed there paying 1,500 naira everyday but things got worse and worse.
I decided to be going out to hustle, to help people doing business or something like that.
Along the line, still nothing was working out.
When I would finish work, after working hard they would give me 200, 500 at the highest 1,000 naira.
I was not able to pay for the house rent again.
Even sometimes, we would sleep without eating.
Everything was upside down, it has been too stressful on my side.
On Friday, I was trying to get home, I was walking on foot because I can’t always afford the bus -
sometimes when I enter the bus, they push me down.
I was trying to get home on foot when I got a call around 12 o’clock.
It was an evangelist calling me from The SCOAN.
I asked what the problem was.
They said they had found my wife and kids at their street.
I asked what had happened.
They said they were crying, saying they had not been eating and no one knows.
I shed tears and from there, I managed to get to this place.
I want to first of all thank the man of God for taking care of my wife from that Friday.
Mr Egesi & Family
Sharing Life Experience
You can see how pathetic the situation is.
We quite understand that it hasn't been easy at all.
Let us listen attentively.
I want to first of all thank the man of God for taking care of my wife since that Friday to this moment;
I want to thank him so much.
From that time till now, that is how we are.
This is how I came to The SCOAN.
I thank the man of God for the help he has given to my wife
and I am still begging him if he can help them so they will be able to achieve
what they want from the man of God.
My own is different, there’s no problem, I’m a Nigerian.
We thank God Almighty for this moment.
We believe that man of God will definitely come to your aid.
"To spend more on others and less on ourselves".
We are going to hear from the man of God very soon.
Whatever the man of God is going to do, we will be able to assist you and take you out of the
problem you are facing and wipe out your tears, in Jesus' name.
After accommodating Mr Egesi and his family and listening to their pitiful life experience, T.B. Joshua
and the Emmanuel TV Partners assist them to enable them to get back on their feet with a renewed hope
and a fresh beginning.
Good Morning Church!
[Good Morning.]
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Christie Pua.
I am 37 years old.
I am from Indonesia.
These are my children, Frederick and Blessing.
The man standing beside them is my husband, John Kennedy Egesi.
I want to thank the man of God for what he has done for us for more than one week now.
He has accommodated me and my little family.
He was giving us pocket money and everything was free for us here in The SCOAN.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
I would like to plead to the man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world.
Please help me and my children to go back to Indonesia.
Good Morning Church!
[Good Morning.]
I want to take this opportunity to thank Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world
and the man of God for taking care of my family for the last week.
I thank him so much.
May God be with him.
My name is John Kennedy Egesi.
I am from Imo State, Nigeria.
Thank you so much.
I want the Man of God to help my wife and kids get back to Indonesia.
For myself, I know my own miracle is on the way.
God will help me.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
My name is Frederick.
I want to thank the man of God for what he has done for us all this time we have been here.
Thank you.
I thank God that I’m not going back to picking up bottles from the dustbin to sell.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
Right now, we are here to give you a message from our father in the Lord - Prophet T.B. Joshua,
on behalf of himself and Emmanuel TV Partners worldwide.
First and foremost we want to speak to our brother, the father of the children and the husband to our sister
from Indonesia.
Prophet T.B. Joshua wants to assure you sir, that he is going to help you to find a job.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
Secondly, he said that he is here today to give you the sum of 500,000 naira
That is for our brother here - the sum of 500,000 naira for him to start a new life here and get himself back
on his feet again.
Please my brother, the message from Prophet T.B. Joshua is, "do not use your legs to walk again
to Alaba market. With this money take care of yourself. Don't use your legs to walk again".
Once again; Prophet T.B. Joshua is sending you this gift of 500,000 naira for our brother here.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
For our sister here from Indonesia who has stated publicly that she was requesting help
from the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua to return to Indonesia with her children;
the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua said that ministry here the SCOAN and Emmanuel TV Partners
are going to take up your travelling back to Indonesia.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
With your two children the ministry will take care of getting all of your travel documents,
getting your passports, every document you need, your flight tickets to the sum of USD 7,000,
for your and your two children.
Aside from all of the cost that it would take to transport you back to Indonesia, Prophet T.B. Joshua
and Emmanuel TV Partners are additionally giving you the sum of $3,000 USD so that you can start
a new life afresh in Indonesia with your children.
Your two children will be given a scholarships to the various educational levels back in Indonesia.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
Mr John Kennedy Egesi Receives The Sum Of 500,000 Naira From T.B. Joshua And Emmanuel TV Partners
Mrs Christie Pua & Children Receive $3,000 USD From T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
Once again brethren, this is the message from our father in the Lord, Prophet T.B. Joshua for himself and
and Emmanuel TV Partners worldwide who have heard about that case.
As we said - as Christians we cannot afford to look the other way when we see our neighbors in trouble.
Our sister came in tears to The SCOAN.
She was on the street with her little children.
Today, to the glory of God, the mission of Emmanuel TV - you can see it in the life of this family;
"Changing lives, changing nations and changing the world".
Thank you, man of God!
Thank you, Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world.
I want to thank all of you.
May God continue to bless you.
May God continue to pour the Anointing on the man of God to reach the troubled world.
Amen. Let's put our hands for Jesus Christ!
Man of God, I am speechless now.
Thank you for helping my husband also.
I still love my husband.
The Family Receives 500,000 Naira & USD $3,000 USD From T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
Thank you man of God for what you have done for my family.
Thank you Emmanuel TV Partners.
Thank you for all you have done for us.
They are giving us $3,000 USD to go back to Indonesia.
They will pay for our tickets and give us scholarships so we will not go back to picking up bottles on the road.
Thank you man of God.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
I thank the man of God so much.
Now, I don’t need to move around on foot anymore.
Nobody will push me down from the bus.
I thank you so much, man of God.
A bundle of thanks.
Only good will be seen in this life.
Nothing will come upon you, in Jesus' mighty name, I pray. Amen.
TESTIMONY TIME
This is really marvelous to see the transformation that is happening in the lives of the people.
This family's life has really been transformed.
They came here in tears of sorrow.
God Almighty used His anointed servant Prophet T.B. Joshua to transform their life.
It was indeed a radical transformation.
Truly, we cannot afford as Christians to look the other way when our brother is in need.
We have been called as Christians to respond to all human needs; for that is what love entails.
We have seen the manifestation of this in the life of the family.
We can see them with smiles of joy.
We can see a big difference.
We saw them first time when they came to The SCOAN some weeks ago.
Anybody would hardly recognize this family some weeks ago because you see that something marvelous,
something wonderful, a great transformation has indeed occurred in their life.
We give glory to God Almighty.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ!
We are going to hear directly from them, how God Almighty has indeed blessed them.
Can we just hear from you?
What you have to say concerning what God has done in your life?
Good Morning, Church!
[Good Morning.]
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Help me to thank God for everything He has done for me and my little family.
Mrs Christie Pua & Family
My name is Christie Pua.
I came from Indonesia.
I am 37 years old.
As you have seen before in the video, those were the things that brought me and my little family
to The SCOAN looking for the favour of the man of God.
The video as you can see is our past.
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
We are here today to thank God for everything He has done for us
and to thank the man of God for allowing himself to be an instrument and problem solver for us.
I also want to thank the Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world
and The SCOAN for what they have done for me and my little family.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
As you were watching the clip; when you came to The SCOAN, there were some complains you made.
You also made your request known to the man of God, Emmanuel TV Partners and viewers all over the world.
Today, can you tell us what can you say about your request that has indeed been made?
I really thank God for everything.
Man of God has made our wish come to pass.
Here is my passport and my children’s documents and as you can see here,
these are our tickets to go back to Indonesia for me and my children.
We heard from the lady; the first time she came to The SCOAN the complain was that only she had a passport
but her children had no documents.
Despite the fact she had a passport, there was not way she could have traveled back to her country.
That was a complain she made.
We give glory to God that today man of God has indeed rescued them out of that terrible situation.
As we heard from the woman - what she said just now; that the man of God has indeed
procured them a passport.
We can see her holding her own passport and two passports of her children, that were procured
by the man of God.
Not only that; she has pointed to the documents we have seen on the board next to them.
These are tickets for their travel back to their country - Indonesia.
We want her to go beside the board and explain to us what the documents are all about.
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
These are our airline tickets provided by the man of God for me, my son and daughter.
These are the documents I need for me as a Nigerian’s wife.
We are going back on Tuesday.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully!
That clap is not enough for Jesus!
Put your hands together louder and louder for our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ!
This is a woman that came here crying, in pain and sorrow because they were in a terrible situation.
All hope was lost.
She never had any idea for getting out of this problem.
But through His Anointed Servant - Prophet T.B. Joshua, whom God has been using to bless millions and millions
all over the world - today, their life is transformed.
Today, she can talk about procurement not only of the passports and documents for her children but also visa
and tickets for the travel back and to start life anew in their country - Indonesia.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for the living God!
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
Not only that, the man of God has spent a lot of money on us for our documents, accommodation
and all the necessary things that have to do with us.
Altogether, it is about six million naira.
Thank you.
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
We heard her earlier speaking in the clips that she was given a sum of $3,000 USD
to establish her financially when she gets back to her country Indonesia.
We also watched how the husband was given a sum of 500,000 naira, to establish himself financially here.
A visa for her and passports for her children were procured, together with traveling tickets
and all necessary documents, aside from the fees and expenses for transportation to be able to procure
these documents.
She is telling the whole world that this money sums up to 6,000,000 naira.
Let us put our hands together for our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.
We give glory to God Almighty.
Madam, having seen what God Almighty has done in your life; can you tell us what you have to say about
our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ?
What advice you have for millions and millions of people listening to you all over the world, regarding what God
had done in your life?
Before I give my advice, I would like to thank The SCOAN evangelists.
Since we have been here, they have been preparing us spiritually.
The man of God has catered not only for our physical needs but also spiritual needs as well
for us to keep hanging onto God.
My advice to those all over the world and everyone here is, “Don’t run from God; run to Him"
because God has something to say in every situation.
Amen.
Hallelujah.
We have heard from the woman that she was blessed not only financially;
her spiritual life has also been enriched.
Since she has been here at The SCOAN she spent time listening to the Word of God
and her spiritual life has indeed been enriched.
We give glory to God Almighty.
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
We want to ask our sister a question.
We know that God Almighty never considers our past in order to determine our future.
God Almighty has indeed forgiven our past; the past of the sister, her children and her husband as well.
We want to ask you sister; can you tell the whole world and viewers all over the world
that are listening to you right now - with a hope you will not disappoint your husband, since God Almighty in His
own infinite mercy has wiped away your past and given birth to your future -
can you tell us that you don't disappoint your husband and you see through to him?
Yes.
We are still going to continue communicating because it doesn't matter where we are.
It is only distance that is between us but our love and care cannot be separated by distance.
Thank you.
Thank you, man of God.
May God bless you abundantly and give you long life and prosperity.
Anything you touch shall prosper, in Jesus’ name.
Amen. Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
We have heard from the woman that she just promised the whole world that she would not
disappoint her husband.
Even though they may be far apart physically, the distance does not affect their marriage and their union.
Their love remains and the love of God will continue to hold them forever.
Once again, put your hands together for Jesus Christ!
Right now, we want to hear from the husband.
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
Hallelujah, we give glory to God for what we are witnessing right here at the live Sunday Service
at The SCOAN.
We are so much blessed by watching what God has done in the life of this family.
We have one more question for you madam.
As you are going back to your country Indonesia with your two children, we want to ask you,
"Are you going to train up your children in the way of the Lord, so as they grow up they will not depart from it?"
The whole world is watching.
They have witnessed what God Almighty has done in your life.
These children are now under your care.
Observing the evil happening all around the world, we want to ask you one more time,
"Are you going to train up your children in the way of the Lord, so as they grow up they will not depart from it?"
Yes, I promise to train my children in the way of the Lord by the grace of God, in Jesus’ name.
Amen.
Hallelujah, we give glory to God.
We have heard from her a promise to the whole world that she will train up these children
in the way of the Lord.
Man of God always advises us that we should follow God's instruction for our life, and His instruction
will set us on the good route to the good life.
We give glory to God Almighty.
We heard from the wife.
We now want to listen to the husband.
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
Sir, you are welcome.
Can you introduce yourself and tell what you have to say concerning what God has done in your life?
Good Morning Church!
[Good Morning.]
I am very happy.
I am John Kennedy Egesi from Imo State, Nigeria.
I am very, very happy about what the man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners have
done in the life of my family.
I am very happy about that.
I want to use this opportunity to thank them so much.
I am more than happy at this very period because if you watch me now and watched before,
you will see that I am like a bank manager now.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
This man is appreciating God for what He has done in his life.
Indeed, if you watched the clips from their arrival to SCOAN and you see them now, hardly you will recognize
that it is the same person.
Not only his spiritual and financial life has been transformed but also the physical appearance.
Looking at them, you can know that God has indeed done something wonderful and marvelous in their life.
The brother can not contain this, as he speaks out and glorifies the Name of God to the whole world.
Once again; put your hand together for the miracle working God.
Hallelujah.
I am so happy; I really want to thank the man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners across the world.
I am thanking the evangelists for the way they helped us here with accommodation and everything else here.
I really thank them so much.
The man of God supported me also with the sum of 500,000 naira.
Now, I cannot be pushed out of a bus and I won’t travel by foot anymore.
I will be able to establish my life before my wife and children come back again.
I really thank the man of God.
John Egesi & Family
Testimony Time
We have heard from the brother who said that with that gift of 500,000 naira he received from the man of God -
Prophet T.B. Joshua, his financial life has been totally transformed.
He will be now able to establish himself financially out there, in the world.
No more running around on bare foot, no more being humiliated or embarrassed in the public,
because God indeed has used His anointed servant Prophet T.B. Joshua to bless him financially.
Hallelujah, we give glory to God Almighty.
Right now, I am bouncing in the Lord.
I want you to help me to really thank the man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners.
I am very joyful and happy about all the blessings I have received here.
Not only that but opening doors of breakthrough; so many people who didn’t call me before
have started calling me.
John Egesi & Family
Testimony Time
There are a lot of breakthroughs now with calls here and there.
There was even one of my brothers whom I called a long time ago
and I know he did not see the clips but it is the effect of the prayers here -
this the arena of liberty for sure!
John Egesi & Family
Testimony Time
What I was planning before now, the doors are open, in the mighty name of Jesus.
I am really happy about that.
Hallelujah, let us put our hands together once again for Jesus.
We have heard from the brother that since he entered The SCOAN;
apart from the financial and spiritual blessings that he has received from the man of God
Prophet T.B. Joshua, all the breakthrough doors have been opened.
He has been receiving breakthroughs in every area of his life.
Coming of this woman to The SCOAN has brought family union and immense blessing in their lives.
We give glory to God Almighty.
We want to ask the husband one vital question.
As your wife will be travelling to Indonesia with your two children and they are going to start a new life there
in Christ Jesus,
and the wife was asked the question earlier and she made a promise, we want to ask you a question,
"Are you going to promise the whole world now that you will remain faithful and loyal to your wife,
even while you are not together physically?"
She knows quite well that sometimes I can make calls for two hours when we are not together,
talk less of now that the hand of God is involved.
For sure, we will continue to be together; distance is not a barrier.
You have heard the promise from the husband that distance is indeed not a barrier,
that although they may not be together physically but the love of God is binding them together.
He will remain truthful and faithful to the wife.
We give glory to God Almighty.
He said that communication would not be a problem.
We give glory for this restoration of peace, unity, happiness in this family.
God Almighty has indeed established them financially.
Their spiritual life has been transformed and today they can talk of a new life in Christ Jesus.
Children of God, million thanks is not enough to glorify the Name of God
for what He has done in the life of this family.
Who could have justly done this?
It is none other than our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.
They came here in tears of sorrow, discomfort, pain but today tears of sorrow have been totally wiped away,
by God Almighty through the Anointed Servant Prophet T.B. Joshua, and we give Him all the glory.
Put your hands together once again for our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.
Finally, we want to hear from the son.
We know he will also have something to say concerning what God has done in their live.
John Egesi & Family
Testimony Time
People of God - Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Frederick.
I thank man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners and people who work here
for all they have done for us since we have been here.
I thank the man of God for everything he has done for us.
He made our passports, got visas and paid for our tickets to go back home to Indonesia.
God bless you, sir.
You will never lack, in Jesus' name.
Frederick & Family
Testimony Time
Because of what the man of God has done for us, I will not go back and be picking up bottles to sell
and in the process of that, receive many insults.
My past is already my past indeed.
I will not go through that again.
Frederick & Family
Testimony Time
I thank all of you – viewers, man of God, Emmanuel TV Partners for all you have done for us.
Please, pray for my father.
We give glory to God for this day of testimony in your life.
Your family is a living testimony to the mightiness and goodness of God in lives of the people.
It can educate the people out there that may be in the same condition as this family was before.
No matter the situation you may be going through; you should trust in the goodness of God Almighty.
Continue to appreciate Him because faith requires us to speak before we see or feel the result.
We give glory to God Almighty that today we are happy and rejoicing in the Lord for what He has done
in the life of this family.
That is what Christianity is all about.
The man of God says that we are indeed called as Christians to respond to all human needs.
We appreciate God Almighty for using His Anointed Servant Prophet T.B. Joshua to transform the lives
of these people.
Today they can go back there and start a new life in Christ Jesus.
Once again, let us put our hands together beautifully for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ.
Hallelujah.
We have heard from them what God has done in their life and we give glory to God for His mightiness
and goodness in their life.
As the wife has said, she would be travelling to her country to start a new life and the husband too,
has been established financially, spiritually here.
He has promised that distance is not a barrier; the love of God still stands and holds them together.
We give glory to God Almighty.
I want to advise you, as the children of God.
The God Almighty has done mightily marvellous things in your life.
He has done all this for the salvation of your souls.
Make sure, wherever you may be, to continue to follow His instruction daily for your life.
Make sure, as you promised madam, that these children will be trained up in the way of the Lord,
so when they grow up they will not depart from it.
We look forward to see you very soon with more and more testimonies of fulfilment of God's blessings
and promises in your life.
Once again, let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Christie Pua & Family
Testimony Time
Once struggling in abject poverty in a foreign land, now God has wiped away the tears of Mrs Egesi
and her family.
She is about to travel back to her country together with her children.
My name is Mr John Kennedy Egesi.
I thank God so much for the way The Emmanuel TV Partners and the man of God,
Prophet T.B. Joshua took care of my family, our accommodation and everything.
Even all the ticketing and travel documents costing up to six million naira.
I thank God so much.
More grease to his elbow, amen.
The man of God has also established me with 500,000 naira so that I can be able to get back
on my feet and meet up with them in Jakarta, Indonesia
and they will also come back and meet me here.
I am very grateful.
I thank the man of God so much.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Christie Pua.
I am very happy.
I want to thank God and the man of God for this wonderful moment.
I am very grateful to the man of God.
He helped us, provided travel documents, air tickets
and all our accommodation costs since we have been here.
I thank God; I really thank God.
As we are about to go, we met the man of God in his office just now and he was asking me
what my future plan was and I told him my heart desire to build an orphanage in Indonesia.
I am an orphan and I know what it feels like to be an orphan.
I have passion to help the needy, those who are less privileged.
The man of God was very happy with my future plan.
He also assisted me and has given me $3,000 USD.
I will start to build my orphanage and help people, in Jesus’ name.
Amen.
Thank you very much.
The man of God said that apart from the $3,000 USD he has give you to establish yourself, now he wants to add
another USD 3,000 for this wonderful plan of building an orphanage.
This is another support.
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank you, man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners.
Upon hearing of her desire to build an orphanage, Prophet T.B. Joshua further blessed them
with another sum of $3,000 USD.
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank you, man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners.
My dream has come to pass and I will come back to give my testimony by the grace of God, in Jesus' name!
Amen.
Now, I am going back to my country with $6,000 USD.
Thank you.
Now madam, as you are going back to Indonesia, your country with your two children; what message
are you taking back to Indonesia?
Emmanuel!
John Egesi & Family
Charity Testimony
I am addressing my Indonesia people that they should come and feel the presence of God
at The SCOAN.
I assured them that once they came to the arena of liberty, their lives would never be the same,
in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Emmanuel.
My name is Frederick.
I am very happy today for what God has done for us.
We are going to Indonesia now.
We are going to the airport now to catch our flight to Indonesia.
I thank the man of God and the Emmanuel TV Partners for all the expenses -
buying our tickets, passports, visas and everything, blessing my mum and dad.
They did everything for us; I am so happy.
We will come back with a testimony, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
My name is Blessing.
Daddy T.B. Joshua I love you.
Dancing for joy, the Egesi family thank God for using Prophet T.B. Joshua to transform their case.
Mr Egesi & Family
A million thanks is not enough for how God has restored this family.
As Mr Egesi embraces his family as they get ready to embark on their journey, he is also at peace
as the man of God has blessed him with the sum of 500,000 naira to establish himself in Nigeria.
Mr Egesi & Family
After a long and painful struggle he has found rest in the house of God, where Prophet T.B. Joshua took in him
and his family, accommodated them and made all their travelling arrangements to start a new life.
As the Bible says in Psalm 30:5, "weeping may stay for the night, but joy comes in the morning."
Mr Egesi & Family
Bye, bye daddy!
Take care of yourself.
Thank you, man of God.
Thank you, Emmanuel TV Partners.
Thank you, SCOAN ministry.
Thank you to everybody involved.
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
Amen.
May God bless you all.
As the bus will take them to the airport drives out of the SCOAN, Mrs Egesi and her children are well equipped
to start a new life.
Not only has the Prophet T.B. Joshua financed the entire trip but also blessed them with $3,000 USD
for their welfare, and the further $3,000 USD for the project of an orphanage in Indonesia.
What you make happen for others, God will make happen for you.